[theme music playing]
You won't support any other
candidate? Just Arnaldo?
You can count on me, Congressman.
There's no turning back, Ivy.
I may be far away,
but you have my full support.
Now's the time to establish
a new government.
A government that will truly understand
the problems of its people.
A new Ardiente!
-Long live Diego!
-[all] Long live Diego!
As your next governor,
I promise you that we will take this town
-to even greater heights.
-[applause]
I want you to support my bid for governor.
Why would I lend you money?
You know my loyalty lies
with your son, Arnaldo.
Oh, really?
These pictures I have of you
say otherwise.
[Ivy] If I were you,
I'd fire your investigator.
You're humiliating yourself.
Who do you think is capable
of leading this town?
-Aside from us, the Ardientes?
-Me.
I will run for governor
against you, Arnaldo.
[crowd clamoring]
[mouthing] Diego!
[Arnaldo] I saw you earlier.
You helped Diego.
Ow. First, we aren't together
for you to feel jealous.
Once you're ready to talk
in a calm manner,
I'm sure you know where to find me.
What are you doing there?
Get out of my room!
-Do it again.
-I said leave--
No, because I will keep
coming back for more.
For a politician, you're quite perverted.
Be careful.
That might get you into trouble.
-Ivy, the congressman's here.
-May I join you?
What are you doing here, Congressman?
We weren't expecting you.
[Julio] Surprise!
Well…
perhaps this is a bad time.
Congressman, whatever you're thinking,
nothing happened between me and Arnaldo.
The truth is, he was just
about to leave, right?
[chuckling] I was just about to say
that you two look like
you've been swimming.
-Mm…
-[all chuckle]
Nevertheless, before we leave, Miss Aguas,
I would like you to know
that whatever relationship
you have with Arnaldo,
I support it.
To be honest,
I was expecting that you'd
bring it up to the next level.
-Next level?
-Yes!
Why, do you plan on rejecting Arnaldo?
Grandpa.
[Julio] I won't allow Miss Aguas
to dump you just like that.
Congressman. Are you suggesting
a shotgun wedding?
[Julio clears throat]
I hope we don't come to that.
[tense music playing]
Uh…
Ivy, that's not what Grandpa meant.
No. Actually, that's exactly
what I mean to say.
You two would make a good couple.
So, why should we wait any longer?
I believe the two of you should
get engaged as soon as possible!
Then we could all move on to
more important matters,
like the upcoming election, am I right?
Wow. Well, Congressman, I just want to say
that I don't believe
in relationships of convenience.
I simply don't. I'm not like
the women you trample on.
I'm different. I have thorns.
If you force Arnaldo,
your favorite grandson might
come to regret his decision.
[scoffs]
Well, I appreciate your
concern, but Ivy's right.
We have to wait for the perfect time.
I agree.
But I do hope the perfect time
comes very soon.
You know, Miss Aguas,
I'm an impatient man.
Now, if you will excuse us. Good evening.
Take care, Congressman.
[Julio speaks in Spanish]
Thank you, pretty lady.
[tense music playing]
Nanny. What you saw in the room earlier…
you do know that meant nothing, right?
I didn't want it to happen.
But I had no choice.
Arnaldo is instrumental to my plans.
Ivy. How long are you going
to keep playing this game?
Jepoy is gone.
No one else is going to protect you.
[Diego]I will.
[romantic music playing]
I'll protect Ivy.
Ivy, I saw Grandpa and Arnaldo
with their bodyguards.
Did they harass you?
No, Diego. The congressman
was just forcing me on Arnaldo.
What?
Ivy, don't let him.
There are other ways
to bring down the Ardientes.
-You don't have to put yourself?
-Diego…
of course, I won't let him.
I'll control the Ardientes,
not the other way around.
Okay, Grandpa. What was that about?
[Julio scoffs]
I want your charades
with Miss Aguas to end.
You need to focus on your
campaign, not on that woman.
You're being too slow.
I told you, Grandpa,
Ivy isn't that kind of woman.
She's not easy. She's different.
She needs time and attention.
She must be good in bed.
Arnaldo…
It's okay to fall for her.
[tense music playing]
But don't ever fall with her.
I know what I'm doing.
Don't interfere with my plans.
That's the way you want to play it?
Fine by me.
Keep this in mind, though…
I still hold the rope
that you are climbing.
And I won't have any second thoughts
of dropping you like a hot potato…
if your plans get in the way of mine.
Remember that.
[ominous music]
Ivy, I'm sorry.
I'm just concerned about you.
And I wish you could just
stay away from Arnaldo.
Diego, thank you
for your concern. I understand.
Like you said, Julio is cunning,
and Emilia is suspicious of me.
As for Arnaldo…
he's wrapped around my finger.
I can get evidence from him,
which we can use
against their family.
That's why I need Arnaldo.
Let me help you, then.
Ivy, I'll watch over you.
I'll do everything I can
to put an end to this.
Thank you, Diego.
[crickets chirping]
[ominous music playing]
[sighs]
No one else can ever have you, Ivy Aguas.
You're mine.
[ominous music continues playing]
Nanny, has he left?
Not yet. He's still outside.
Says he wants to stand guard.
What?
[romantic music playing]
You know, Ivy…
somehow, I feel at ease.
Even if Jepoy's not around,
I know Diego's here.
He'll make sure you're safe.
[suspenseful music playing]
[thunder cracking]
I'M HERE.
[car approaching]
[suspenseful music continues playing]
Raul. Shouldn't you be heading home?
Your wife might suspect us.
[chuckles] And you…
I'm sure you'll get into a lot of trouble.
[chuckles] That would be great.
At least then I'll have a reason
to kill her.
Maybe all of them.
My only mistake was that
I didn't kill Julio.
Wait a minute.
Why are you suddenly mad at the Ardientes?
Did something happen?
You know, I don't like being
asked too many questions.
You know what?
We can help each other, Raul.
Help me investigate my dad's death,
and I'll give you everything you need.
[chuckles]
Money, power…
anything you need to protect yourself
from the Ardientes.
What do you say?
[suspenseful music playing]
Auntie, I don't how Papa's
distrust came to this.
Arnaldo doesn't even respect me anymore.
If this continues, Auntie…
I'd forever be just
a trinket in this house.
We can't let that happen.
-We need to fix this.
-How?
What do you want me to do, Auntie?
Have my own son killed? I can't do that!
Of course not!
Arnaldo's your son.
There must be some other way.
Papa just needs to see how much
voters prefer me over Arnaldo.
How?
[tense music playing]
[Georgina] We'll continue pressing charges
against the Ardientes,
but we need new pieces of evidence.
Well, I'll take care of it, Attorney.
I'll talk to Arnaldo
and have him confess on record
that he killed our witnesses.
But it would also help
if we can find Arthur.
I'll have him investigated, then.
I have a feeling that he's still alive.
If he isn't, then why can't
they find his body?
Diego. I need your help too.
I want you to weaken
the Ardientes' influence
on the people.
So, continue rallying against them.
One of the things I plan to do
is to conduct a survey.
The public is losing their trust
in the Ardientes.
Once that happens, their allies
will start doubting them.
Then, their influence on the
justice system will also weaken.
When that happens, we'll open our case.
You can count on me, Ivy.
Thank you, Diego.
That's all, everyone. I have to go now.
-My dear.
-Bye, Nanny.
-Diego. Thank you.
-Be safe.
Attorney.
[Julio] I'm glad Miss Aguas
joined us today.
The truth of the matter is…
I was a bit worried.
I thought I turned you off last night
since I was very aggressive.
But you know, Miss Aguas…
Much as it pains me
to admit this, I'll say it.
I'm not getting any younger.
And I want to see the day Arnaldo finds
the perfect woman he can settle down with.
And of course, I want to see
my future great-grandchildren.
-[clears throat]
-[Julio] The next generation
that will carry the Ardiente name.
Papa, can you not put Ivy on the spot?
She and Arnaldo
are still dating, you know.
They'll get there, anyway.
Papa, I think we should instead
discuss how to eradicate Diego.
[ominous music playing]
I don't see any reason
why we should worry about Diego.
If he stirs things up,
I'll take care of him.
[Emilia] Arnaldo, you can't be
that violent all the time.
I don't think Ivy will like it.
Your mom is right. I agree with Emilia.
Less people dying means less controversy.
Why don't we conduct a survey, instead?
Let's find out
what the public really thinks.
[upbeat music playing]
Mister, please give me
something to eat. I'm hungry.
-Here, take this.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you, sir.
Diego, why are we here?
Nanny, I just want to know
what's going on here.
Because I'm sure the people here
are being abused by the Ardientes.
Oh!
I thought we came to buy
more of the vegetables
Pandoy sells here.
[chuckling]
So you want to know
what their situation is.
You'll start campaigning soon, won't you?
You're off to a good start!
But you should prepare
these hands of yours,
-okay?
-[chuckles]
You'll be shaking a lot of hands today.
-Come on, Nanny.
-You better ready those hands.
[Diego] Look at this, Nanny.
I need to talk to Dionesia Agustin.
I know her! It's Miss Diony.
She often buys her vegetables from us.
She owns a stall
in the middle of the market.
-Let's go see her.
-Okay.
Wow, Ivy.
Would you believe
I have the same idea as yours?
Why don't we hire
a research team for this?
[upbeat music playing]
Is the research company
you'll hire trustworthy?
[laughs incredulously]
Are you trying to imply something?
No, I'm… I was just asking.
Well, a survey will be a waste of time.
We already know what
the public will say, don't we?
That we, the Ardientes,
can still be trusted.
Actually, Grandpa, I think Ivy's right.
You know, better be safe than sorry.
I'll have someone do the survey
as soon as possible,
but not with the research
company you'll hire.
I don't want any issues with that survey.
[scoffs]
Survey this, survey that.
It doesn't matter.
[suspenseful music playing]
Please, I beg you.
I haven't sold anything yet.
-Give me your money!
-I need it for medicine--
-I can't remember the last time you paid.
-Just for now, please. I'm begging you.
-I said hand over your money!
-Please, sir.
-I'll take this.
-No, sir. Please.
-Give it to me!
-This is for my meds--
-[Diego] Hey!
-[Loring] Miss Diony!
What's wrong with you? Why'd you hurt her?
-[Diony] They took my money!
-Hey. Hey. What's this?
That's illegal! Give her back her money.
And if I don't? What are you going to do?
You extortionists deserve to be punished.
[Diego grunting]
Hey, wait! Stop that!
-Where's your spunk now, huh?!
-[Loring screams]
Hey!
-[loud thud]
-[groans]
-[crowd clamoring]
-Take that!
Go on! Get 'em!
[women yelling]
[clamoring]
[Loring] And don't you ever come back!
Thank you for your help, Ivy.
I'll leave the survey to you.
Mm-hm.
I trust the research company you gave me.
Thank you. And don't worry.
I'll handle it.
So, then… I'll see you
at the municipal office?
Looking forward to it.
Bye.
Let's go.
[Emilia clapping] Whew. Wow! Slow clap.
[laughs] Like a true thief in the night.
-What is it now, Emilia?
-Ivy, do you think…
I'll just let you leave
without asking you why you stole my idea?
No, I didn't. I didn't steal anything.
Let's just say that your dad and Arnaldo
trust me more than they trust you.
That's the thing, Ivy. Something is off.
I'm starting to doubt whether
I should trust you at all.
Emilia, why wouldn't you?
I did everything to help you.
-All I want is to--
-Bring down the Ardientes.
Right?
You know what? You are a two-faced bitch.
[scoffs] You made me believe
you'd help and support me.
Then what? You dropped me
like a hot potato.
Why are you mad at me?
Shouldn't you be mad at yourself?
You knew from the very start
that I wanted to support you.
But what did you do? Look at yourself.
Emilia, you're beautiful,
and your clothes are nice.
But you're boring.
You're not in public office
anymore. You're powerless.
Right, Miss Claire? Look at Emilia.
Doesn't she look like a tomato
past its prime?
Am I right? Excuse me.
Your son, Arnaldo, needs me.
[tense music playing]
Bitch! [chuckles]
Thank you, Diego. I'm so glad you came.
-Don't mention it.
-Aren't you an Ardiente?
You're the Congressman's grandson, right?
Aren't those guys working
for those abusive Ardientes?
What are you doing here
if you're an Ardiente?
Are you going against your own family?
[indistinct chatter]
Yes. Because I found
out the truth about them.
[pensive music playing]
The rumors about the Ardientes'
crimes are true.
[crowd murmuring]
You might not believe me,
but I know you're sick and tired
of what they're doing.
It's time to start making
a change in this town.
We should all unite for a new Ardiente!
-[vendor] For a new Ardiente!
-[crowd] For a new Ardiente!
[crowd clamoring]
-Long live Diego!
-[chanting] Long live Diego!
Thank you! Thank you!
[vendor] Thank you.
[pensive music playing]
Diego, you did a great job.
I knew change would come,
but I never imagined
it would be this fast.
Tomorrow, we'll start the survey.
The vendors will be
a great help with our plans.
The people are sick of being abused.
So it wasn't difficult to convince them.
Mom, do you have updates
on the search for Arthur?
Actually, we're just waiting
for the investigator.
-Ma'am.
-Oh.
Any updates? What's new?
Ma'am, we've searched
every funeral home and hospital
that could lead us to him,
but we didn't find him.
Does it mean that he's still alive?
It's possible, ma'am.
But we're still following another lead.
It's possible he's been dumped in a river.
[suspenseful music playing]
[sighs] If that's true,
I hope he managed to survive.
Thank you.
-You're welcome, ma'am.
-Thank you.
Mom, keep looking for him.
We'll focus our efforts on the survey.
We'll surprise them.
Before they know it,
their supporters will be gone.
Are you ready to be the governor?
Governor Diego Torillo.
Yes, I am.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] You can leave now.
I'll take care of that bastard.
So, should I get rid of Diego now?
[door closes]
Can you really kill your own brother?
Remember this, Arnaldo.
You both came from Raul, your father.
I like the hunger that you're showing.
But…
I want you to think this through.
Let's just say…
this will be your initiation.
Through this, I will know
if you're just mad for power.
Or if you'll be a wise and capable leader.
You already know the answer, Grandpa.
[snickers]
[sighs]
[dramatic music playing]
Good morning, everyone!
I'm here to conduct a survey.
[woman] A survey?
[researcher 2] Are you ready to answer?
[respondents] Yes.
Here are the questions…
[researcher 1] Are you happy and content
with the administration
of Poblacion Ardiente?
[no audible dialogue]
Are the local officials
of this province honest?
[researcher 2] Will you vote for them
in the upcoming election?
Are you rooting for
another candidate aside
from the ones
in the current administration?
[researcher 1] Please write down
the person's name.
[no audible dialogue]
WHO IS YOUR PREFERRED CANDIDATE?
DIEGO TORILLO
Our approval rating is down by 40 percent.
My popularity as mayor
went down to 60 percent.
Surprise, surprise!
Diego is gaining popularity,
and a lot of people believe
that he is a potential candidate.
I can't lose to Diego.
I won't let that happen!
[breathes deeply]
[pensive music playing]
[Carlotta] All our efforts
weren't in vain.
If the Ardientes' rating
went down by that much,
that means a lot of people believe us.
We might've lost in court
and had our case dismissed…
but now the people of Poblacion
Ardiente see the truth.
[pensive music playing]
[Diego] Nanny! Nanny, Uncle!
-It's Diego!
-Hey, everyone!
Nanny, Uncle, check this out.
-What's that?
-Wow! He got high ratings!
So, that means, we aren't
the only ones rooting for you!
A lot of people believe in you too!
-We won the survey!
-[Pandoy laughs]
Diego's got a shot
as governor of the new Ardiente!
[people cheering and applauding]
-Diego for a new Ardiente!
-[chanting] Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego…
[sighs]
Mom?
[sniffles]
Are you crying? What's wrong?
Nothing, dear.
I'm just glad to see what's happening.
And it just so happens it's your
father's death anniversary.
[sniffling]
You miss Dad, don't you?
Do you want to visit him, Mom?
Okay. I'm allowing you to visit him.
I just have to make arrangements,
-so you can visit him safely.
-Just me?
How about you, Lily?
I want to, Mom, but, I can't.
You know that the Ardientes
are keeping an eye on us.
I won't give them a chance
to find out who I really am.
I know Dad will understand. Right, Dad?
[Ivy exhales heavily]
It's just a survey.
I can still change that.
I know you can.
But it can't hurt to be careful
and practical.
Do you know that Diego is the dark horse…
who can destroy our dreams
and tarnish our name?
Order a news blackout for that survey.
The public must not know about this.
-I already did.
-Good.
Now, starting tomorrow…
we will work hard to regain
the supporters we lost.
The Ardientes imposed a news blackout
for the results of this survey, right?
But I guess, you'll still publish it.
Of course.
This is information that
the public deserves to know.
Good to hear that. Thank you.
I'm glad people like you still exist.
-Here.
-Thank you, Miss Aguas.
It's part of my job.
I'm not a journalist who can be bribed.
I'll be going now.
-Okay. Again, thank you.
-Thank you.
[pensive music playing]
-Ivy.
-Thank you, Nanny.
You know, dear,
I do enjoy seeing you like this.
Your heart seems to be at peace.
-[chuckles softly]
-[tender music playing]
You know what's missing?
Your mom, here in the house.
The both of you, Nanny.
I want you both here in my house.
I'm very lucky.
I have two mothers.
No, dear. I'm the lucky one.
You see…
even though I never got the chance…
to marry and have children…
at least I was given a chance
to be a mother to you.
You know, dear, you complete me.
[sniffling] Remember that, okay?
-Nanny.
-Hmm?
Why are you crying?
I don't know. [chuckles and sniffles]
[chuckles] I guess, I must be getting old.
I think it's better for us
to relax tonight.
-Do you want some wine?
-[giggling]
-I'll just get a bottle.
-No, I'll do it.
-Just stay here.
-All right.
[tender music playing]
[phone ringing]
-[tense music playing]
-[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
[line ringing]
Answer the phone!
What is wrong, my son?
Is it Ivy? She's not answering your calls?
You nearly broke your phone.
[tense music playing]
[sighs] My poor son.
Why can't you accept the fact
that Ivy's just playing you?
Actually, playing us.
You know, she always supports
the ones on top.
Who knows? Maybe she's with
Diego, the star of the survey?
Diego, Diego, Diego! Will you stop?!
-Oh.
-Hmm?!
-Can you just leave me alone?!
-Oops.
Don't take your anger out on me.
If I were you,
I won't just sit down there.
Look at you, drinking.
What you should do now…
is go to Ivy and see
who she's busy flirting with.
[dramatic music playing]
[crickets chirping]
[sighs deeply]
Papa.
Looks like you've had one too many drinks.
That's bad for you. You might
have another heart attack.
Especially if you pair that
with your problems.
I don't need your advice, Raul.
Do you remember…
that you're the reason
why I had a heart attack?
[chuckles] Get out of my sight.
But, Papa, I've brought
food to match that.
Do you want some?
[sighs]
If you don't leave now while
I can still stop myself, Raul…
-I might just--
-Wait a minute.
To be honest, Papa…
I'm so sick of you. You're all talk.
Your mouth moves,
but you never do anything.
That's all you're good at, right?
Don't worry.
After I kill your son, Diego…
you'll be next.
Or maybe you'd rather die together?
Hmm?
Did you know, Raul…
that Emilia's the only one
stopping me from killing you?
[Julio chuckles]
So you should be careful.
Because a poor weakling like you…
with a flick of my hand…
-I can stop your heartbeat.
-[scoffs]
Go on then. Get out of my face.
Get out! You blood-sucking leech!
You know, Ivy… you're so different
from the scared little girl
I took care of.
Now, I'm the one scared for you
because you're so brave!
Nanny, I got my courage
from a lot of people…
Miss Prianka, my dad, my mom, and you.
-You're brave too!
-[giggling]
I know you don't hear this often
because I don't always tell you this, but…
I love you so much, Nanny Carlotta.
I love you as my own mother.
My dear…
You're making me cry again!
Nanny, you've been crying all night!
[laughing] Come on. Let's take a selfie.
-What?
-[giggling]
I need a new wallpaper.
-Hang on.
-You know what a selfie is?
Of course I do!
-Okay, then.
-How do you do this?
I was still a kid in your wallpaper.
-There we go.
-There. Smile, dear.
[shutter clicking]
That's a cute pose, Nanny Carlotta.
I think you've had…
-too much to drink!
-[Diego] Ms. Carlotta, Ivy!
-Diego!
-Diego.
I can't contain how happy I am.
According to the survey, we have
a huge lead over the Ardientes.
-[Carlotta giggles]
-Nanny.
I'll get you a glass. Stay right there.
-Okay.
-Thank you, Nanny!
[uplifting hopeful music playing]
[knocking on door]
[ominous music playing]
Who's there?
[latch clicks]
Raul, come in.
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm taking the deal you offered.
But I need a huge amount
of money in exchange
for the information you want
regarding your father's death.
Okay.
So, who is my father's killer?
Is it Emilia?
Arnaldo?
Or, is it you?
[suspenseful sting]
[gun clatters on floor]
Ivy, thanks so much again.
At least, we got to celebrate.
[soft piano music playing]
I'll see you out, Diego.
Even if we managed to lessen
the Ardientes' supporters,
we shouldn't rest easy, Diego.
Our enemies are really powerful.
Ivy, I don't care how powerful they are.
Nothing is impossible when I'm with you.
That's why I believe that
we can get through all this.
Once that happens, I hope that you can…
finally open your heart to me.
[sighing] Diego, we already
talked about this.
The only thing I can promise you…
is that nothing will change.
Lily will always be there for you.
[car approaching]
[ominous music playing]
I understand, Iv--
I mean, Lily.
[suspenseful music playing]
All right.
I'll be going now.
Uh, Diego, one more thing…
I want to ask a favor from you.
What is that?
Tomorrow is my father's death anniversary,
and Mom wants to pay him a visit.
Can you go with her tomorrow?
Of course, you can count on me.
Thanks.
You should go now.
Head back in.
-Go inside now.
-Diego.
[ominous music playing]
Nanny, I need to leave again.
They found a lead on Arthur's whereabouts.
I'll be back soon.
Ivy!
-Move aside. Ivy!
-Mr. Mayor!
[screams]
Ivy, get out of there! Open the door!
-Nanny?
-Ivy! Ivy, dear. The m--
-[screaming]
Nanny Carlotta?
[wailing]
Who did this to you?!
[theme music playing]